http://blog.craftygoat.com/privacy-policy.html

« How to Make Bottles of Hope |
Main
| Advertise on CraftyGoat's Notes »
Privacy Policy
At blog.craftygoat.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by blog.craftygoat.com and how it is used.
Log Files Like many other Web sites, blog.craftygoat.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons blog.craftygoat.com does not use cookies.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on blog.craftygoat.com.
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to blog.craftygoat.com and other sites on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:
Google Adsense Commission Junction Amazon
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on blog.craftygoat.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
blog.craftygoat.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. blog.craftygoat.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Posted by Angela Mabray on April
8, 2009 at
9:58 AM
Search
Search this blog:
About this Site
CraftyGoat's Notes is all about sharing polymer clay tips & tricks that have worked for me. (And even a few that haven't!)Read more about CraftyGoat's Notes...
Links
My Book: Polymer Clay 101
My Favorite Blogs
Buy My Book
Categories
Blog News
CraftyGoat.com News
Currently Working On...
Select a Month...
Enter your address to get CraftyGoat's Notes by email:Delivered by FeedBurner
Subscribe to this blog's feed
[What is this?]
